<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Cryptid Tracker</title><link>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Cryptid Tracker</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 04:35:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hawaiian Giant Shrimp</title><link>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/hawaiian-giant-shrimp/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Dec 2022 04:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/hawaiian-giant-shrimp/</guid><description>The Hawaiian Giant Shrimp (Litopenaeus hawaiiensis) is a species of shrimp found in the shallow waters around the Hawaiian Islands.
Description The Hawaiian Giant Shrimp is the largest shrimp species in the world, with adults reaching up to three feet in length and weighing up to 10 pounds. It is a carnivorous species, feeding on small fish and invertebrates. It is an aggressive predator, using its large claws to capture and kill its prey.</description></item><item><title>Hawaiian Night Bear</title><link>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/hawaiian-night-bear/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 04:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/hawaiian-night-bear/</guid><description>The Hawaiian Night Bear (Ursus mauiensis) is a species of bear native to the island of Maui in Hawaii. It is a small bear, with adults weighing between 100 and 150 pounds.
Description The Hawaiian Night Bear is a nocturnal creature, emerging from its den at dusk to forage for food. It feeds primarily on fruits, nuts, and insects, and is known for its skill at climbing trees to access hard-to-reach food sources.</description></item><item><title>Pacific Northwest Air Jellyfish</title><link>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/pacific-northwest-air-jellyfish/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2021 04:35:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zhade.dev/cryptid-log/posts/pacific-northwest-air-jellyfish/</guid><description>The Pacific Northwest air jellyfish (Aequarea aeronautica) is a species of medium sized jellyfish characterized by their ability of airborne flight.
While commonly referred to as a distinct species, the Pacific Northwest air jellyfish is in fact a stage of the common Aequarea aequorea jellyfish.
Description Aequarea aeronautica is a large sized jellyfish, with an average size of 6 to 8 inches in diameter. Its habitat ranges from the upper Pacific Northwest in Canada down south to Northern California.</description></item></channel></rss>